<text>
   <title>Other-Life In-Game Rules</title>
   <info>
      <short>Click on a rule to see its full text. If you have any doubts or questions, ask for clarification with the #help_me command.</short>
   </info>
   <rule>
      <short>Use common sense.</short>
      <long> Use your common sense, until the community decides be conservative about what will or wont be allowed</long>
   </rule>
   <rule>
      <short>Keep Channels 'Clean'.</short>
      <long>Keep the channels 'clean' and when possible, on topic. As the community decides and grows this will change as needed</long>
   </rule>
   <rule>
      <short>Post Ideas in Forum.</short>
      <long>If you have discussions in channel about game improvements or changes, try to get the ideas into the forums so more people can provide feedback and they don't get lost</long>
   </rule>
   <rule>
      <short>Things will change.</short>
      <long>What we have is just what we're starting with, things WILL be changing</long>
   </rule>
   <rule>
      <short>Do not use bad proxy.</short>
      <long>Due to spammers, hackers, etc, use of a proxy known to be used for illegal or abusive purposes will not be permitted. Using private proxy systems that have not been abusing the Internet is permitted.</long>
   </rule>
   <rule>
      <short>Alts shall not interact.</short>
      <long>Characters or Alts shall not interact in any way with other characters run by the same player in any way. It is best if you don't even have an Alt at all. This is not limited by IP or who is running the character at the time of the offense. Other players should not assist by being middle men or help or they may be included in punishment. Punishment can include losing all items or all characters!</long>
   </rule>
   <rule>
      <short>No black market gc sales.</short>
      <long>No gc Sales for RL $'s etc / aka no black market gc sales</long>
   </rule>
   <info>
      <short>All rules here may be subject to change or addition at any given time.</short>
   </info>
   <info>
      <short>Last updated 20-07-2017</short>
   </info>
</text>